A Finding Aid to the Robert W. White Papers, 1889-2003, bulk 1915-2003, in the Archives of American Art AAA.whiterobe
Archives of American Art
- Artifacts, 1973; Series 9; (Boxes 7; 0.1 linear feet)
  - Printing Block, Image of Robert White's Sculpture of Stephanie White, circa 1965 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Printing Block, Image of a Landscape, undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Insignia Patch, undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Photographs, circa 1940s-2001; Series 10; (Box 8; 0.5 linear feet)
  This series includes photographs and snapshots of Robert White, White's studio space, Claire Nicolas White, various family members and friends. Most of the individuals in the personal photographs are unidentified. There are interior and exterior shots of the Whites' residence in St. James, New York. Files also include negatives and a transparency of White's artwork.
  Included are slides of the casting and finishing of Robert White's General George Pershing Memorial and artwork used by the artist for reference purposes.
  Other photographs and slides can be found in Series 2: Correspondence and Series 3: Project Files.
  Photographs are arranged in chronological order.
  - Photographs of Robert White, Family Members, and Friends (Box 8)
    - Robert White, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Robert White in His Studio, circa 1960-1987; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
    - Claire Nicolas White?, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Claire Nicolas White with her Family in Rome, Italy, circa 1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Various Family Members and Friends, circa 1970s-1982, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Personal Photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Robert White's Residence, Moriches Road, St. James, New York (Box 8)
    - Exterior Views, 1995-1998, undated; (5 folders) (Box 8, Folder 8-12)
    - Interior Views, 1995-2001, undated; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 13-15)
  - Photographs of Artwork, 1950s-1992, undated; (19 folders) (Box 8, Folder 16-34)
  - Photographs of Exhibition Installations, 1969-1976, undated; (5 folders) (Box 8, Folder 35-39)
  - Negatives of Various Sculptures, undated; (5 folders) (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Tranparency of the Taylor Head, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Slides (Box 8)
    - General George Pershing Memorial Casting and Finishing, 1989; (Slide File 1) (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Pershing Memorial Casting, 1989; (Slide File 2) (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Pershing Memorial Casting and Miscellaneous Slides of Artwork, 1989, undated; (Slide File 3) (Box 8, Folder 44)